ettu.org 2019-12-04

# ETTU.org - Privacy Policy

**ETTU PRIVACY POLICY**

This page summarises the privacy policy and practices of the European Table Tennis Union hereunder referred as ETTU.The ETTU Privacy Policy has been established to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679. The policy is subject for updates and amendments.

**What kind of information is collected?**

If you visit the ETTU website to browse, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about the visit. The following information is automatically collected and stored:

  * The Internet Protocol address will be saved anonymous so there is no access on further relating information. We make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting;
  * Information relating to your computer system, such as the type of browser and operating system, language used, and demographic information such as global location;
  * The date and time of the visit; and
  * The web pages or services accessed.

Information collected automatically in this manner is used for purposes such as assessing system performance, improving web services, improving website management and determining best content for our visitors, partners and sponsors. The ETTU website does not automatically gather any specific personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, or email address. We only obtain personal information in a manner where you provide consent.

**What safeguards are in place?**

The ETTU website makes reasonable security arrangements to protect your personal information against such risks as unauthorised access, collection, use, disclosure, or disposal. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation, and day-to-day operating practices as part of the ETTU’s continuing commitment to the protection of personal information it holds.

**Cookies**

The ETTU uses "cookies" to track how our visitors use this site, demographics on their systems, languages, global locations, and sites previously visited or to determine which site content most appropriately fits our visitors, such as topic specific content. The cookies are not used to identify individuals. Cookies can be disabled or denied in your web browser settings with minimal impact on your ability to access information from this site. However, many other websites will not function properly without them.

( _A "cookie" is a file that may be placed on your hard drive without your knowledge by a website to allow it to monitor your use of their site.  Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device. They are created when you visit a website that uses cookies and are stored in the memory or hard drive. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information about the visitor’s experience and interests. The information is generally used to make content and services more relevant and useful. For more details about cookies visit _[_www.allaboutcookies.org_](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/))

**Google Analytics**

The ETTU website uses Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilises the data collected to track and examine the use of the ETTU website ([www.ettu.org](http://www.ettu.org/)), to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualise and personalise the adverts of its own advertising network.

The Google Analytics' features that the ETTU has implemented are based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings, which can be found here: [ **https://www.google.com/settings/ads**](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

The ETTU will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless we have obtained a visitor's prior consent to that data merger.

Visitors can also make use of the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, which can be found here: [ **https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

**Disclosure of third party services**

The ETTU works withthird party services for the capturing, storage, review and analysing of data. Thesethird party services are bound by their own privacy policies. The ETTU is not responsible for the privacy practices of these service providers. Thesethird party services providers with whom the ETTU works and whom may, but not necessarily, be able to access personal information or web data pertaining to the ETTU website are:

  * TTM Online entries([https://www.ttm.co.at/onlineentries/users/login](https://www.ttm.co.at/onlineentries/users/login))
  * Google Analytics ([http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)&[http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html))

  * Sportradar AG (Feldlistrasse 2, CH-9000 St. Gallen, Switzerland, VAT identification number CHE-113.910.142 MWST) (<https://www.sportradar.com/about-us/privacy/>)

**Links to other sites**

Visitors should be aware that the ETTU website contain links to websites not operated by the ETTU. If you visit these websites, you will leave our site. When you visit these other sites, the ETTU privacy policy will not apply, although you may be subject to the privacy policy of that new site, if one exists. The ETTU is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of external websites.

**How can I access and correct information I submit to the ETTU website?**

The ETTU will inform an individual, upon the individual's request, of the existence, use, and disclosure of the individual's personal information, and shall give the individual access to it in accordance with the law. Individuals may access and verify any personal information with appropriate notice so that the office is able to supply the information required.

**ETTU members**

This part refers to the ETTU member Associations including their delegations for any ETTU competition called hereafter the members.

The same privacy policy as above applies to the members. Members’ information such as their legal seat, Presidents’ and other names including contact details are displayed on the ETTU website as provided by the members.

**Further data as provided by the members to ETTU may also be stored, used and published.**

The members, while entering their delegations for ETTU events either via the ETTU online entry system or via email registration confirm with their entry to be in possession of the explicit consent of each person of their entered delegation agreeing with the ETTU privacy policy. When an entered person being aged under 16 years, the member shall be in possession of the same explicit consent from that person’s parent(s) or legal tutor(s).

The ETTU will use the entered data for result management and display and overall event management. The entered data will be kept by ETTU as long as ETTU needs it to safeguard the continuation of its events.

Results of competitions, news stories, players’, clubs’ and team Rankings, names etc will be displayed on the ETTU website and stored by the ETTU. The reason to keep these data available is to safeguard the European Table Tennis history, the news and information for all visitors, press, media and others.

At ETTU competitions and events, pictures may be taken by photographers of the players and any person present at the competition. These photographs remain the property of the photographer and the ETTU. The ETTU has the right to use these pictures wherever it may need.

At ETTU competitions and events, matches, interviews etc may be filmed for television and internet streaming. These recordings remain the property of the ETTU.

The ETTU has the right to display these recordings on its website and other (web)sites and TV channels, to sell them directly or via a third party.

By registering and entering (physically) an ETTU event, the person agrees to abide by all ITTF and ETTU rules and regulations, directives, prospectus and ETTU Privacy Policy. All registered/entered Associations and individual players, coaches, medicaland other persons agree to be under the auspices of the ETTU and its agents in all matters concerning television coverage, video, internet web casting, motion picture coverage, and photographic coverage of any kind. Participants release all rights, or rights held by their agents or sponsors, in all matters relating to television and web casting coverage, video and motion picture coverage, and photographic coverage of any kind. A participant’s refusal of above listed coverage may be subject to suspension or dismissal from the competition/event.

**Enquiries and Complaints**

All enquiries and complaints regarding your personal information or our Privacy Policy should be forwarded to the ETTU office:

European Table Tennis Union (ETTU Asbl)

73, rue Adolphe Fischer

L-1520 Luxembourg

Luxembourg

Email: [privacy@ettu.org](mailto:privacy@ettu.org)

Telephone: +352 223030
